[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "This is when I cry, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "when", "I", "cry", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "You're not vain at all like that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "vain", "at", "all", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "It's just -- it's not what my life is about.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "--", "it", "'s", "not", "what", "my", "life", "is", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Literally a pair of socks?", "question_tokens": ["Literally", "a", "pair", "of", "socks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Literally a pair of socks.", "answer_tokens": ["Literally", "a", "pair", "of", "socks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Wouldn't it be the chronic debt cure?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "it", "be", "the", "chronic", "debt", "cure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Yes, I probably should write -- I called my publisher when all the debt business was going on.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "probably", "should", "write", "--", "I", "called", "my", "publisher", "when", "all", "the", "debt", "business", "was", "going", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "NNS", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Where are the safe havens for people?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "the", "safe", "havens", "for", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I think the number one safe haven where people put their money is to invest in yourself first.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "number", "one", "safe", "haven", "where", "people", "put", "their", "money", "is", "to", "invest", "in", "yourself", "first", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "It means if you're -- if you use what I talk about, first diagnose the problem.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "means", "if", "you", "'re", "--", "if", "you", "use", "what", "I", "talk", "about", ",", "first", "diagnose", "the", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Is this when I cry, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "when", "I", "cry", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "What is the way that people at the moment that haven't got much money, how can they find fulfillment without necessarily material things?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "way", "that", "people", "at", "the", "moment", "that", "have", "n't", "got", "much", "money", ",", "how", "can", "they", "find", "fulfillment", "without", "necessarily", "material", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "-- who was -- you were part of a program to help him, right?", "question_tokens": ["--", "who", "was", "--", "you", "were", "part", "of", "a", "program", "to", "help", "him", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "How do you think he's doing in particular relation to the economy of this country?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "in", "particular", "relation", "to", "the", "economy", "of", "this", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well, I think he's doing very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Better -- what better place to do this?", "question_tokens": ["Better", "--", "what", "better", "place", "to", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "You don't want -- listen, you don't want to talk about what's going on out there at a birthday party.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "want", "--", "listen", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "out", "there", "at", "a", "birthday", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "So what was he like?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "was", "he", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "ARPER: I completely agree with you.", "answer_tokens": ["ARPER", ":", "I", "completely", "agree", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Is he aggressive when he gets wind up?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "aggressive", "when", "he", "gets", "wind", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Yes, I -- you know, he plays hard and he wants to win.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "--", "you", "know", ",", "he", "plays", "hard", "and", "he", "wants", "to", "win", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Do you worry for him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "worry", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "You know, one thing that I've come to realize is that polls reflect present day fears, not future results.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "one", "thing", "that", "I", "'ve", "come", "to", "realize", "is", "that", "polls", "reflect", "present", "day", "fears", ",", "not", "future", "results", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "When you see the Republican candidates to date, what do you make of them?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "Republican", "candidates", "to", "date", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "I think that they have a pretty strong field.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "they", "have", "a", "pretty", "strong", "field", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Who do you think is the most dangerous?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "is", "the", "most", "dangerous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Dangerous isn't the best word.", "answer_tokens": ["Dangerous", "is", "n't", "the", "best", "word", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Who's the one the next time you see the president you say, \"You just want to watch that one\"?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "one", "the", "next", "time", "you", "see", "the", "president", "you", "say", ",", "``", "You", "just", "want", "to", "watch", "that", "one", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "``", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "''", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Do you understand that, and what do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "that", ",", "and", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "You know, I -- folks are able to have their own opinions, and I would never censor anyone and say they're wrong for their own opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "--", "folks", "are", "able", "to", "have", "their", "own", "opinions", ",", "and", "I", "would", "never", "censor", "anyone", "and", "say", "they", "'re", "wrong", "for", "their", "own", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Does he have that thing in him to say, right -- like he might be doing now with America?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "have", "that", "thing", "in", "him", "to", "say", ",", "right", "--", "like", "he", "might", "be", "doing", "now", "with", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "I think you're painting an analogy that he's losing right now, and I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "'re", "painting", "an", "analogy", "that", "he", "'s", "losing", "right", "now", ",", "and", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Is that inaccurate?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "inaccurate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "I don't -- I -- it's actually inaccurate, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "--", "it", "'s", "actually", "inaccurate", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Is he winning, though, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "winning", ",", "though", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "We are winning.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "winning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Was he a good come-from- behind kind of guy?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "a", "good", "come-from-", "behind", "kind", "of", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "So if you take any kind of assumption that he's not in a winning position right now, you'd back him to win?", "question_tokens": ["So", "if", "you", "take", "any", "kind", "of", "assumption", "that", "he", "'s", "not", "in", "a", "winning", "position", "right", "now", ",", "you", "'d", "back", "him", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Absolutely, without question.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "without", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "You won't hold it against me that you used to be on my college bedroom wall?", "question_tokens": ["You", "wo", "n't", "hold", "it", "against", "me", "that", "you", "used", "to", "be", "on", "my", "college", "bedroom", "wall", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "No, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "It's a compliment?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "compliment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, it is a compliment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "is", "a", "compliment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "``", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "But I've got such respect for you watching your career from extraordinary journalist, to \"The Apprentice.\"", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "'ve", "got", "such", "respect", "for", "you", "watching", "your", "career", "from", "extraordinary", "journalist", ",", "to", "``", "The", "Apprentice", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "How did that happen?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "A lot of sweat equity.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "of", "sweat", "equity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Did you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "What made you think that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "you", "think", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "RELAND: I just knew it.", "answer_tokens": ["RELAND", ":", "I", "just", "knew", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Have you had much failure?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "much", "failure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Oh, my goodness, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "goodness", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Where is the failure?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "the", "failure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Well, first of all, you're very kind.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "you", "'re", "very", "kind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Because I haven't seen it?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "I", "have", "n't", "seen", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Oh, my God.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Literally a pair of socks?", "question_tokens": ["Literally", "a", "pair", "of", "socks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Literally a pair of stocks.", "answer_tokens": ["Literally", "a", "pair", "of", "stocks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "That's a totally different thing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "totally", "different", "thing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "It's extremely different.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "extremely", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "What was the key -- when you began with the socks and stuff, what was the key moment for you that really propelled this from, you know, a small business into the big league?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "key", "--", "when", "you", "began", "with", "the", "socks", "and", "stuff", ",", "what", "was", "the", "key", "moment", "for", "you", "that", "really", "propelled", "this", "from", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "small", "business", "into", "the", "big", "league", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Well, in the beginning, our socks were carried at a handful of sporting good stores, Big Five and a few others.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "the", "beginning", ",", "our", "socks", "were", "carried", "at", "a", "handful", "of", "sporting", "good", "stores", ",", "Big", "Five", "and", "a", "few", "others", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Do you remember what it was?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "what", "it", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Sure, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What's the answer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "What kind of injuries?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "injuries", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Smashed up face, nose, smashed teeth, ripped shoulder, mouth, lips, eyes.", "answer_tokens": ["Smashed", "up", "face", ",", "nose", ",", "smashed", "teeth", ",", "ripped", "shoulder", ",", "mouth", ",", "lips", ",", "eyes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "What did you learn about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "The minute it happened I thought, OK, this is going to be an adventure.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "minute", "it", "happened", "I", "thought", ",", "OK", ",", "this", "is", "going", "to", "be", "an", "adventure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "How important is it, do you think, to have -- if you are doing this kind of business, to have the backdrop of a good, stable family?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "it", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "to", "have", "--", "if", "you", "are", "doing", "this", "kind", "of", "business", ",", "to", "have", "the", "backdrop", "of", "a", "good", ",", "stable", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "For me, it's everything.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "me", ",", "it", "'s", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "But none of the models?", "question_tokens": ["But", "none", "of", "the", "models", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Some of them, like a few of them.", "answer_tokens": ["Some", "of", "them", ",", "like", "a", "few", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Who did you think was -- present company excepted, who did you think was the number one, the most beautiful model you have ever seen?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "did", "you", "think", "was", "--", "present", "company", "excepted", ",", "who", "did", "you", "think", "was", "the", "number", "one", ",", "the", "most", "beautiful", "model", "you", "have", "ever", "seen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CD", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "There are so many.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "so", "many", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "ORGAN: If you could produce one magazine, say one \"Sports Illustrated\" before you died, and you could put one woman as the cover, it can't be you?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "If", "you", "could", "produce", "one", "magazine", ",", "say", "one", "``", "Sports", "Illustrated", "''", "before", "you", "died", ",", "and", "you", "could", "put", "one", "woman", "as", "the", "cover", ",", "it", "ca", "n't", "be", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", ",", "VB", "CD", "``", "NNS", "VBN", "''", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Oh, my goodness.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "goodness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "There were so many.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "were", "so", "many", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "A what?", "question_tokens": ["A", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "The pair of you.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "pair", "of", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What was that experience like for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "experience", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "It still doesn't -- I still feel like she's here.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "still", "does", "n't", "--", "I", "still", "feel", "like", "she", "'s", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "A proper star, wasn't she?", "question_tokens": ["A", "proper", "star", ",", "was", "n't", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Absolutely, in every way.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "in", "every", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "As someone who knew her so well, what was something that really annoyed you the most about the way she was characterized?", "question_tokens": ["As", "someone", "who", "knew", "her", "so", "well", ",", "what", "was", "something", "that", "really", "annoyed", "you", "the", "most", "about", "the", "way", "she", "was", "characterized", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "People always said she was dying.", "answer_tokens": ["People", "always", "said", "she", "was", "dying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "What's the thing you are pushing now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "thing", "you", "are", "pushing", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Our business is about solutions.", "answer_tokens": ["Our", "business", "is", "about", "solutions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "Do you have a little laugh at them now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "little", "laugh", "at", "them", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "You know, it was interesting, because for years we were building our brand very quietly.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "was", "interesting", ",", "because", "for", "years", "we", "were", "building", "our", "brand", "very", "quietly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110905pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Do you like that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "I'd say a slow learner, hopefully tough.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "say", "a", "slow", "learner", ",", "hopefully", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]